<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News | Karan Muvvala</title>
    <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>News</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/media/icon_hu89548756f618d3133e4bd8d0014fa73c_37105_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted for presentation at IEEE Aerospace Conference, 2023. Click Here for details!</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-08-02-ieee-aeroconf23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-08-02-ieee-aeroconf23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Paper Title: REASON-RECOURSE Software for Science Operations of Autonomous Robotic Landers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- Project Name: NASA COLDTech --&gt;
&lt;!-- Abstract: Future planetary exploration missions on the surface of distant bodies such as Europa or Enceladus can’t rely on human-in-the-loop operations due to time delays, dynamic environments, limited mission lifetimes, as well as the many unknown unknowns inherent in the exploration of such environments. Thus our robotic explorers must be capable of autonomous operations to ensure continued operations and to try to maximize the amount and quality of the scientific data gathered from each mission. To advance our technology toward this goal, we are developing a system to maximize the science obtained by a robotic lander and delivered to scientists on Earth with minimal asynchronous human interaction. The autonomy architecture consists of two main components: REASON (Robust Exploration with Autonomous Science on-board) and RECOURSE (Ranked Evaluation of Contingent Opportunities for Uninterrupted Remote Science Exploration) for efficient and useful scientific communication between scientists and robot. The key advantage to this design is in its ability to continuously operate and adapt despite the constraints of high-latency, low-bandwith communications and an uncertain environment which today would require ground-in-the-loop operations. This paper presents the initial version of the REASON-RECOURSE system. Details of the implementation of the scientist interface and interaction with the ground software - RECOURSE - and the on-board robotic planning software - REASON - are given. Demonstration of the operation using NASA&#39;s OceanWATERS testbed will be shown. --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An extended abstract got accepted at RSS 2022 Workshop on Risk-aware Decision Making;</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-06-01_rss22_worshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-06-01_rss22_worshop/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected for RSS Inclusion 2022 Fellowship</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-05-01_inclusion_fellow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-05-01_inclusion_fellow/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected for IEEE RAS Travel Grant for ICRA 2022</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-04-01-icra22_travel_grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-04-01-icra22_travel_grant/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted for presentation at IEEE Int&#39;l Conf. on Robotics and Automation (ICRA), 2022. Click Here for details!</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-02-01-_icra22_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2022-02-01-_icra22_paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Paper Title: Let&amp;rsquo;s Colloaborate: Reactive Synthesis for Robotic Manipulators using Regret Games.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One paper accepted for presentation at IEEE Aerospace Conference, 2022. Click Here for details!</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-08-01_aero_conf_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-08-01_aero_conf_paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Paper Title: Expert-Informed Autonomous Science Planning for In-situ Observations and Discoveries&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Project Name: NASA COLDTech&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abstract: Future planetary exploration missions on the surface of distant bodies such as Europa or Enceladus can’t rely on human-in-the-loop operations due to time delays, dynamic environments, limited mission lifetimes, as well as the many unknown unknowns inherent in the exploration of such environments. Thus our robotic explorers must be capable of autonomous operations to ensure continued operations and to try to maximize the amount and quality of the scientific data gathered from each mission. To advance our technology toward this goal, we are developing a system to maximize the science obtained by a robotic lander and delivered to scientists on Earth with minimal asynchronous human interaction. The autonomy architecture consists of three main components: Shared Science Value Maps (SSVMs), which function as an interface between REASON (Robust Exploration with Autonomous Science on-board) and RECOURSE (Ranked Evaluation of Contingent Opportunities for Uninterrupted Remote Science Exploration) for efficient and useful scientific communication between scientists and robot. The key advantage to this design is in its ability to continuously operate and adapt despite the constraints of high-latency, low-bandwith communications and an uncertain environment which today would require ground-in-the-loop operations. This paper presents the overview of our architecture and initial results on the development of such a system. These results will focus on progress made in developing the details of the SSVM interface between human scientists and robotic explorer and the ability of REASON to act on the SSVM to develop plans on-board that attempt to maximize science obtained while being guaranteed to respect any relevant system and safety constraints.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started my PhD at the Aerospace Engineering Science Department at CU Boulder</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-05-15_phd_offer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-05-15_phd_offer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An extended abstract got accepted at RSS 2021 Workshop on Robotics for people</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-05-01-rss21_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-05-01-rss21_paper/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Successfully Defended my thesis. For More info click here.</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-04-01-ms_defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-04-01-ms_defense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;: From Autonomous cars, factories to households, we envision a future where robots work safely and efficiently alongside humans. While robots today thrive in industrial and lab settings, we must develop theories and algorithms that will enable the transition of these systems from robot-centric workspaces to the real-world. Hence, we want robotic systems not only to observe and react to the changes in the environment but also guarantee completion of the given task while ensuring safe execution. For robots operating in the presence of humans with non-contradicting goals, it is crucial to work together to save resources, time, and ensuring that everyone achieves their goals. Combining these objectives is challenging given the complexity of the tasks and various ways the system could interact with the environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This thesis blends different theories developed by the Formal Methods, Game Theory, and the Human-Robot Interaction community to develop a Regret Minimizing Framework (RMF) that addresses the above problems. While previous work using these approaches has assumed the human to be either purely adversarial or probabilistic, these assumptions are very conservative and eliminate the possibility of cooperation. This thesis proposes a notion of regret to synthesize high-level strategies for the robot that explores possible cooperation with the human while ensuring completion of the given task within some user-defined bound on the total energy spent by the robot. This work analyzes and implements various notions of regret and reasons about their emergent behaviors. An end-to-end synthesis toolbox is developed to compute regret minimizing strategies, which implements various optimization techniques to help scale the algorithms to the robotics domain and illustrate the efficacy of the optimal strategies through various case studies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Received the Diversity and Inclusion Scholarship from the ME Department at CU Boulder</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-02-05-diversity_scholarship_cu_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2021-02-05-diversity_scholarship_cu_me/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appointed as the Chapter Secretary of the IEEE Denver Computer Science, Information Theory, and Robotics Society</title>
      <link>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2020-12-05-ieee-cir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://muvvalakaran.github.io/post/2020-12-05-ieee-cir/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
